So, yeah. As you can see, we are
milestone three Azure right now, but we
are like 100 Oh, hello.
Oh.
Luckiest finds of all time.
Oh, man.
Um but, we are like level
What's it called? We're level 99 right
now with like 100 more XP, and then we
will have milestone four. So, that is
going to be
what we do right now.
There's actually Yornak right here. So,
pretty cool stuff.
Anyway,
let's get a bath there.
What you can do, you can kind of just
like set up as the round goes.
There we go. Now, we have that there.
They might have an emergency spray here.
I'm going to set up another thing here.
And you can kind of just feel free to
reposition as you go, especially the
seeker bolts because their wind up is
really nice.
But anyway,
let's get our final thing set up.
And now we're set up.
That person up there, I don't want them
disabling that. So, we're just going to
snatch them and get them in here.
Kind of do that.
They're going to get a tropaia much of
tropaia from that.
I saw Yornak is placing a spray over
there.
I'll do it.
Get that two-time dodge, and there we
go.
Where are they going?
Hold on. I saw them place a spray here,
so I'm going to
get rid of that.
They're pretty low HP, so honestly going
after them ain't the worst idea in the
world. They're probably going to place a
spray right now.
They did not.
I am really down stamina there, so let's
just reset chase. They are lagging. Or
was I lagging? Who knows?
Let's go after them. We are all pretty
much set up. There's a two-time there,
so we got to be careful of that.
That triple highlight is really useful.
One more hit. One more hit.
Ooh, why not?
Never mind, still one more hit. We are
not worried.
If we reset chase here, we should,
without interference, be good to go.
And there we go.
Just take a second.
And there we go. I'm actually going to
get my golem over here
since that area was being kind of
annoying, and we don't really have it
covered that much. So, just going to
leave that there. Actually, let me hide
it.
Hiding your golem is a really useful
thing to do because
I mean, of course they're not going to
see it, and then
yeah. I should probably go after that
person
instead of that two-time. We could save
the two-time for the LMS.
Now, let's put pressure on this noob,
though.
They're pretty in the open.
Had to be careful of the two-time,
though.
With that grab.
Just going to keep chasing them. If they
go over there, my golem is going to
destroy them.
They're cooked.
Zone.
I saw him not even hit that.
We have 30 speed, so this is a really up
good opportunity. Holy, I am trash.
Really good opportunity to um
just burst them down.
And I just keep ragdolling them. Oh.
Teleport back.
Oh, the round ends in
What? How much time?
I low-key did not realize how low we
were on time.
I have been like kind of just
dillydallying.
And be like
Throw them into my plant.
We got to be really careful of a clone
fairy.
Are they not going to?
I guess not.
Go for it.
Now, that 07 teleported all the way over
there. So, let's go ahead and go after
them.
That's a clone, for sure. But, does that
mean they're over there?
Ah, it does.
Do not want to have an 07 in the last.
No, sir.
And especially because we could get that
two-time LMS.
If I can get a grab on them, that'd be
really nice, but it's kind of risky
right now.
Just going to reset chase.
Sort of.
This could be really risky, actually.
Yo, where did they go?
I think we just lost.
Oh. Wait.
Oh, they're
Wait, if I switched to my golem earlier,
I would have actually been able to
counter that.
I just kind of was like, oh, yep, okay.
And then I realized, "Oh, wait, my guild
is over there."
Yeah, I could have done that.
Anyways, now that I have milestone four,
I want to give some of my thoughts on
Azure overall.
And something I do want to point out is
what I've noticed after using him for
some time is it feels like
he's the killer you have the least
control with. What I mean by that is
like
the uh
the success of your games can really
depend on if the survivors walk into
your traps or if they don't.
I actually got to place more, honestly,
but hold on. Let me just kill this 07. I
was kind of distracting myself with
talking, but anyway.
As I was saying,
it can sort of feel like the success of
your games, for one, it's really map
dependent, but for two, it's like it's
either the survivors will run into your
traps or they won't. Um some of the
time, depending on the map, like if you
really can't do much about it.
So, yeah, that's kind of something to
consider.
I do have to set up more stuff, I won't
lie. Let's get something there.
And then
just whack him.
And then we'll get something here, and
that finishes up the map for now. I'm
probably going to just reposition my
stuff constantly though. I'm kind of
done stamina here in this chase.
Got to be really careful. I'm going to
go for a grab here, but that chance
could stun me.
Yo, how did you miss that? I'm not even
going to lie.
I tried to throw him at them.
Anyway, let's keep going after this
noob.
I honestly could have thrown them into a
corner or something. That probably would
have been better.
It definitely would have been better,
actually.
I I might have mis-timed that. Did.
Let's go after the chance right now
while they have a lot of a tropa.
V could be a problem later.
Going to have to watch out for the J now
now that we got a crystal thunder our
face.
Ah, yeah. That was pretty bad aim.
What I am going to do right now actually
is going to get a golem.
And then yeah.
I've got to like commit to it J. I can't
lie.
But now let's go after
this Elliot. I think that's the plan.
Going to have to reposition our plants.
I'm going to golem perry if the Actually
we don't have a crystal on us. Oh now we
do.
But no longer valid. So let's go after
the J. They have the most of a tropa or
the chance depending on who
I guess the chance didn't want to move.
There we go.
Oh.
Yeah, I probably should have been ready
to golem perry that.
Oh, thanks.
All right, next uh we either want to
take out the V or the noob probably.
Is anyone in here?
Nah.
See there is Ooh, the V's right there.
There's a spot right there. Let's uh
just get that out with this.
What?
They put it Oh.
Kind of just wasted that.
Yeah, let's go after the V.
Can get a drop on them.
Here we go.
Holy damage. Holy Oh my
Holy quick drop, bro. Dang. Okay.
Crazy golem one-shot combo right there,
but
um
I don't want to leave the newb last, but
the thing about searching for them is it
takes so long. So, I'm just going to
kill the Jane.
Oh, I saw them over there though.
No.
Um are they next to the golem?
Oh, they disabled my plant. I didn't see
that.
Yeah, I think we just got to keep
chasing the Jane though. We have too
much momentum already.
I already know the relative location of
the newb anyway, so
it's honestly fine.
They might try to stun. Yeah, I got to
stay away from that.
There we go.
But yeah, the newb is over there, so
it's good info that we already know
that.
Now, we have to be really careful to not
lose sight of them. If we lose sight of
them,
I have to like There we go.
I have to like keep tabs on every single
um
All right, we cut them off here. They're
running back into our main body. That is
really nice.
I'm just going to keep chasing them with
main body now.
Kaboom.
Kaboom. And
GGs.
Now, another thing about Azure I
definitely want to say,
I mean, he's honestly
I thought he was going to be one of my
favorite killers initially looking at
him, but as I've been playing him,
honestly not.
I I don't know what it is about him.
It's just like
the game just like doesn't feel like
it's in your control. You have to spend
a lot of time setting up. I'm not going
to lie. You
um
setting up your plants does take a good
chunk of the early game,
which can be pretty annoying. It's kind
of like
like so survivors who usually have to
set up up yeah that's
survivors who
usually have to set up
right like they'll just get the time to
set up while you set up and it's can be
really annoying. Like now now we can
actually play the game at full potential
but like actually have to reposition
that secret bulb lucky.
Let's go on this Elliot who is on the
generator.
That looks like the most vulnerable
target right now.
There we go.
I'm going to have to be putting in that
secret bulb to cover both of those
areas.
I mean cover like this area I believe.
So let's uh
Oh that's another thing I don't like
like it you can't um
really like reposition the plant if it's
like nearby so if you want to make like
a slight adjustment uh you kind of
can't.
I'm going to try to jump scare someone
here.
There we go. We got someone.
Oh they're close enough to stun.
Kind of thought everyone got away. That
person just took a lot of damage so we
are going to go after them.
They baited the plant that's
unfortunate. There's also the person who
stunned so they won't have their stun
ready.
I see a spray over there. I don't want
to
use any distance to try and get
good to take note of.
Oh crap.
Okay that was lucky.
Please get caught. Okay nice. It's
really good.
I need to get as much stamina back as I
can.
Oh wait they're dead.
Anyway let's get a golem
hidden over here.
I'm actually going to destroy that spear
while I'm here, too.
And now now we're fully set up.
Now we're fully set up. That took
forever. There is a V Veronica over
there
on like one HP for some reason. I just
grabbed them through that hole.
>> [screaming]
>> And they're dead.
Okay, that's nice.
That is a really good kill.
Um
Try to get this Jane.
Oh, they disabled the plants.
That is not good.
We still got to stay on this Jane. This
Jane has the least stamina out of
everyone.
Okay, we got to be careful of that now.
I'll golem parry if I need to.
So then they don't get shadow point. Oh,
no, we already
Hm.
It's really interesting. I feel like one
of them's going to stun soon. Like
around these corners.
It's pretty scary. I can't really use my
grab right now, either. They'll stun for
each other.
Okay, nice whack.
Someone keeps baiting that plant. That's
really annoying.
Oh.
I was like in my mind for a second.
Okay, that's a good shortcut.
We have our stun immunity up right now,
so we don't even have to worry.
Nice.
Let's um
I mean, this person is just the closest
right now. That's our best bet.
He's getting shot at right now, though.
Is anyone near my golem? No.
If they try to slash, I'm going to uh
I slashed at the same time as them. I
said I was going to golem parry, but I
couldn't because I slashed.
I wish that's That's something I wish um
you could do as a killer just in
general. If you have a parry move, you
should be able to parry like while
you're slashing.
The that works for like John Doe or for
like uh Azure. I really wish that was a
thing.
They avoided my golem and that plant was
disarmed. That's really annoying.
They're disarming my plants really
often.
It's really annoying.
So we gain stamina.
Okay, we have a pretty decent advantage
here right now. We got to be careful of
that Jane Doe. You have that back?
What?
Hopefully I can zone them into my golem.
I'm really hoping they run over there.
If they run over there
Oh, yes.
There we go.
Let's keep going after um
Shoot, where did that 07 go?
Uh then yeah, they went away.
That 07 is probably our
That's bad just cuz I know where they
are. Everyone else we have to look. I
don't know where they are. Wait.
This is really bad.
There's another thing.
I don't know where anyone is.
Oh, there they are.
Oh my god. I don't think I have enough
time to kill them.
I can't even lie to you. Especially if
the other people start helping, which
they definitely should.
If they don't
It's kind of wraps.
Clone just sandbagged a bit. I don't
know why I'm not I should have placed
that a long time ago.
If I placed that earlier and did the
chase, that would have been really good.
Yeah, I I think I should have
repositioned my plant a lot earlier.
This golem has potential to kill really
fast.
If I play it right, but I don't think I
do.
No. Oh, it knocked him so far. Oh, I hit
zero.
I just don't like playing this Like
okay, there's there's a lot of things I
do wrong with this character, right?
There's like
my overall like plant positioning could
be better. I could overall like hot swap
my positioning of my plants a lot more.
I noticed that when I kind of get all
three down, I kind of just avoid getting
any more.
Um in new places, but
overall like Azure just like it feels
like you're the least like in control of
the match, right? It's like the For one,
you are a very map dependent killer.
So,
that's one aspect. For two, it's like in
general your plants are just like as I
was saying earlier,
crap, I forgot about that. Um
I'm kind of like focused on rinsing
right now, but like
in general your plants
are like
you have the least control of what they
do in the match, right?
Like uh
it kind of just depends on if the people
will run into your plants or not, and
yeah, you could constantly reposition
them.
Again, a lot of this is a skill issue.
Azure is a hard killer. You need a lot
of um game sense on like who to
prioritize, who to
um
what's it called? Who to prioritize,
how you should be using your abilities.
How did that not hit the Shalesky?
I should have kept going after the
Shalesky, I can't lie.
Uh hold on, I'm missing all my
attacks.
Um in general the golem too, like using
the golem is a sort of new experience
because it's like
it doesn't have that much uh stamina,
but it it can do a lot of damage if you
use it correctly. It can do
a crap ton of damage.
Anyways, let's go after this noob.
Yeah, in general like I should be
uh switching the posi- Oh, wait, I
should have
hold on.
What the
is happening?
That's the thing there's also a lot of
bugs like um
I don't know. I mean you just saw that
one.
But also
Is there someone in there? I swear I saw
someone in there. Yeah, there's someone
there.
I don't know why they weren't
highlighted while I
put down my down
but anyway yo that sounded sus. My bad
bro.
Anyway
As I was saying
uh crap.
I don't even know what I was saying. I
can't lie to you. It's like 2:00 a.m.
right now and
usually for these types of videos I'll
like actually try to explain like all
right here's what you should be doing,
you know, like
like tips.
I don't even want to do that for a sure.
I'm so sick of playing this killer.
Here's another thing here's XP leveling
is so slow.
It is
They they like nerfed how much it is and
like you wouldn't even get like for a
killer standards, right? Like
even at lower levels like it would take
like
at least two games to level up. Which is
for a killer? Like for a survivor that
makes sense but for a killer's XP it
doesn't make sense that it's that slow.
So it took forever to get this milestone
four.
Um
I've kind of been
playing ass with him. I can't lie.
We're going to have to kill that bee.
Ah.
Thought I could jump scare him.
Now where are those sprays is the
question. I'm going to predict it's like
over here.
Now they were trying to use that.
Healing up with their battery.
There we go. That's one hit.
Holy, my P Shooters are being crazy
right now.
They're going to keep looping there.
Okay. Uh
I should let's use right there.
I'm going to reposition that there.
All right.
I should probably
get a
a gas burner.
That was really stupid tentacle.
Let's place another here.
Going to place another here.
I'm not sure what kind of play that was,
to be honest.
Just going to keep chasing them.
And you're getting thrown in there,
buddy.
Before the slash gets off cool down,
let's just do that. And GG's.
I'm complaining a lot. It's a lot of it
is skill issue cuz like this killer
the five-star difficulty I feel is
definitely warranted. There's you have
to deal with people hiding. You have to
deal with um
constantly repositioning your plants in
actually good spots.
The golem itself is a lot of difficulty
within itself. It's like you're
controlling two killers.
But at the same time, it sometimes
it can be hard to tell if it was your
fault or not, right? Like if there's
like oh, tons of guests in this server
or if
um you just get a bad map. Like let's
say Planet of the Apes, you're
kind of cooked cuz that map is so open
and there there's a lot of darkness.
It's easy to hide, right?
And then
I mean, it also depends on the server.
Like if they if they run into your
plants, then they don't, right? Like
there there's obviously counter play to
that. Like you reposition your plants
and [music] you make use of your golem.
But again, it just feels like a lot of
what happens isn't as in your control as
that of killers and
me personally, I'm not a fan of that.
Like here, okay, let let's try to lock
in here.
All right.
We're going to
We're going to We're going to just calm
down. I'm not going to let I've been
tilt tilt playing for so long.
I've been tilt playing for so long
because I have just wanted to get Azure
like done and over with
so that I could play like a killer. May-
mainly, whenever I face a guest. If I
see a guest, I just lose it, dog.
Huh.
I'm going to throw them into them.
There we go. Triple Oh my god, how many
people did I hit with that?
What is going on?
Sometimes animations are bugged.
Holy stabs.
Uh I got to get my plants down. I forgot
about that yet again.
Let's get this down as we go.
Can I zone them into it?
They lose distance either way.
I mean, they got hit.
Grab them.
Throw them back into the corner.
Zone them again.
Got to be careful of another one.
I got
Anyway.
>> [sighs]
>> Huh. As I was saying,
All right.
I mean, I just got to not have as much
of a skill issue, you know?
I want to get a plant over there. I'm
going to do that right now.
And now I just need to remember to
reposition my plants more. The big
plants don't need to be repositioned.
Uh uh don't need to reposition the
big plants as much, but the small plants
repositioning those can bring you a lot
of what are we doing?
A lot of success.
So, that is something
that has to constantly be kept in mind.
There we go. That's really good.
Holy lag.
Like half the time I strike, I can't
even tell if it's a my lag or
the video time.
So, throw them at the wall.
I don't want to use any stamina to
sprint to a big plant.
Wish I put a secret bulb here. Let's uh
actually do that.
Now, they're pretty boxed in. Oh, no. My
secret bulb over there uh
All right. Now, we're zoning them toward
my secret bulb.
That is some good stuff. There we go.
Anyway,
I think what I'm going to do is actually
put my golem over here.
Just have it here.
I do want to keep it hidden though. If
there is anything I like about the
Master Enforcer in a lot, it's this
golem. The golem actually looks really
cool.
I just grab them down from there.
Get in that plant.
They probably have their slash.
Going to just activate it and then not
go for it.
And there is nobody helping, so this
should be a good kill.
If I manage my stamina quickly, I need
to reposition that secret bulb. And
again, you
I don't I don't like this part. You
can't reposition it like
too close. Um
Let's have to drink a cola. I'm going to
wait for that to run out.
Or I don't want to be last, actually.
Yeah, leaving to be last is probably not
a smart idea. So, I don't see the notes.
That
is nice.
Now,
let's get this tough zone over there.
Yes.
I probably could have slammed them to
rag doll them.
I yeah, I rag doll them into me.
It's really good.
Get that out of there.
I just saw that at the corner of my eye.
Just going to keep chasing them.
They're running into my secret bulb.
That is really nice. Kind of zones them
a bit.
I'm going to get one here. They're using
these boxes a lot.
And then, they can't avoid this.
Cake Factory, I did actually like study
Cake Factory in
the
uh private servers. That's probably
going to be the last game, by the way.
But,
the thing about Azure, right? Azure is
like
the difficulty of Azure is like
different from other killers, right? It
can be kind of similar to John Doe. It's
mostly just like
map knowledge and game knowledge. Like,
a lot of pre-planning goes into Azure,
right? Like, other killers, you can kind
of just react to stuff and it works.
With Azure,
if you are mainly reacting to stuff,
it's not going to work. You have to
pre-plan like where your stuff goes.
Like, especially your golem.
Um cuz that can be really helpful.
And like how you position you and your
golem.
But, yeah.
I'm probably going to take a break from
Azure, but he is pretty fun, actually.
>> [music]
[music]